<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Quartz 4</title>
      <link>https://</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on Quartz 4</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>The Accessibility Project</title>
    <link>https:///</link>
    <guid>https:///</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ An Invitation to Join the Accessibility Project Researchers in the Department of Linguistics at Memorial University of Newfoundland, in partnership with the Newfoundland and Labrador Stuttering Association, are launching a new province-wide Accessibility to Services for People Who Stutter Project fo... ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:38:09 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Community Workshops</title>
    <link>https://learn/community-workshops</link>
    <guid>https://learn/community-workshops</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ Community Workshops Community workshops are a central part of the Accessibility Project. ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:38:09 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Ethics &amp; Values</title>
    <link>https://learn/ethics-and-values</link>
    <guid>https://learn/ethics-and-values</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ Ethics &amp; Values This project is grounded in ethical, collaborative, and justice-oriented research practices. ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:38:09 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Interviews</title>
    <link>https://learn/interviews</link>
    <guid>https://learn/interviews</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ Interviews Semi-structured interviews form the second phase of the project. ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:38:09 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Methods Overview</title>
    <link>https://learn/methods-overview</link>
    <guid>https://learn/methods-overview</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ Methods Overview The Accessibility Project uses a mixed-methods, community-engaged research design. ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:38:09 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Survey</title>
    <link>https://learn/survey</link>
    <guid>https://learn/survey</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ Survey The project begins with a province-wide survey designed to assess: Access to speech-language pathology services Barriers to participation Experiences in schools, healthcare, and workplaces Community and policy gaps The survey is open to: People who stutter Family members Clinicians Educators ... ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:38:09 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>What This Project Is</title>
    <link>https://start-here/what-this-project-is</link>
    <guid>https://start-here/what-this-project-is</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ What This Project Is The Accessibility Project is a multi-stage research and community-engagement initiative focused on identifying and removing barriers to full participation for people who stutter (PWS) in Newfoundland and Labrador. ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:38:09 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Who We Are</title>
    <link>https://start-here/who-we-are</link>
    <guid>https://start-here/who-we-are</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ Who We Are This project is a collaboration among: People who stutter (PWS) Newfoundland and Labrador Stuttering Association (NLSA) Memorial University of Newfoundland (MUN) Educators, clinicians, policymakers, and community allies Our team is committed to ethical, community-engaged, and accessible r... ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:38:09 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Why Accessibility Matters in NL</title>
    <link>https://start-here/why-accessibility-matters</link>
    <guid>https://start-here/why-accessibility-matters</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ Why Accessibility Matters in Newfoundland and Labrador People who stutter (PWS) often face structural, communicative, and attitudinal barriers across health services, schools, workplaces, and public life. ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:38:09 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Declaration of the Right to Stutter</title>
    <link>https://Declaration-of-the-Right-to-Stutter</link>
    <guid>https://Declaration-of-the-Right-to-Stutter</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ We, the undersigned, declare that people who stutter should be accepted as having a stutter. ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>